{
    "id": "a2882d283ebe4b88b646b34f32069cb8",
    "title": "Grammar Check",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6c4b7397d94f47d38975325d22ea3bfc",
            "title": "Grammar Check",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following is the plural form of young one?",
                    "description": "There are no apostrophes in plural nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "young ones",
                        "young one's",
                        "young ones'"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following sentences is grammatically correct?",
                    "description": "We cannot use past time expressions with the present perfect tense.",
                    "answers": [
                        "I have seen him yesterday.",
                        "I saw him yesterday."
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The simple present tense can be used to talk about future.",
                    "description": "The simple present tense can be used to talk about future events that are part of a time table.",
                    "answers": [
                        "True",
                        "False"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The negative form of will is ............................",
                    "description": "In the case of auxiliary verbs, questions and negatives are made without do.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will not",
                        "don't will",
                        "doesn't will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following sentences is grammatically correct?",
                    "description": "Look is a copular verb we use adjectives to modify copular verbs.",
                    "answers": [
                        "She looked happy",
                        "She looked happily",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can you lend me ................................ of butter?",
                    "description": "Pound is a singular countable noun we need an article or another determiner with singular countable nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "pound",
                        "a pound",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have got enough money to buy a car. Here enough is an ...............................",
                    "description": "When enough modifies a noun, it is an adjective.",
                    "answers": [
                        "adjective",
                        "adverb"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is old enough to know better. Here enough is an ......................................",
                    "description": "When enough modifies an adjective, it is an adverb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "adjective",
                        "adverb"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I love ................................ types of cars.",
                    "description": "We use these and those with plural nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "these",
                        "this",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There are no secrets between ....................................",
                    "description": "We use object pronouns after a preposition.",
                    "answers": [
                        "us",
                        "we"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following is not a form of be?",
                    "description": "The forms of be are: is, am, are, was and were.",
                    "answers": [
                        "are",
                        "were",
                        "am",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "My brother loves ...........................................",
                    "description": "We do not normally use articles with plural nouns when we are talking about things in general.",
                    "answers": [
                        "dogs",
                        "the dogs",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}